# **ALEX KAGAME**

(+250) 783 743 221

kagame8732@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-kagame-097096132/

/ Kigali – Rwanda

## **SUMMARY**

Professional IT with a background in computer science. Experienced in different IT related works including IT supporting and reporting, network installation management and troubleshooting as well as Software development skills. I am an upright, dedicated, hard working person that excels at effective communication with others. I strive each day to better sharpen the lives of people I serve and improve my community through my work and services.

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Science in Computer Science** 

September 2014 – December 2018

**Kigali Independent University** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Intern(Andela Technical and Leadership program)

December 2022 - Present

Andela Rwanda

Front end developer

May 2022 - October 2022

HviewTech Group Ltd

Front end developer

May 2021 - April 2022

**Creators agency Ltd** 

IT Technical Assistant of VUP Project

November 2019 – April 2021

**Gasabo District** 

IT Support technician

September 2016 – October 2019

DP Singh&Associates Ltd

### **LANGUAGES**

English – professional working proficient

Kinyarwanda – Native

**French** – Elementary